{
    "results": [
    {
        "question": "Uki-otoshi is part of the Nage no Kata and in English is called:",
        "correct_answer": "Floating drop",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Hand drop",
            "Hip drop",
            "Kneeling drop"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many categories of throwing techniques are there in the Nage no Kata?",
        "correct_answer": "5",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "4",
            "6",
            "3"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "When we practice Nage no Kata we are practicing ",
        "correct_answer": "Throwing forms",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Grappling forms",
            "Free exercise forms",
            "All Judo forms"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Nage no Kata includes:",
        "correct_answer": "Yoko-sutemi-waza",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Shime-waza",
            "Kesa-gatame",
            "Kansetsu-waza"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one of these is not included in the Koshi-waza category in Nage no Kata?",
        "correct_answer": "Uki-waza",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Uki-goshi",
            "Harai-goshi",
            "Tsurikomi-goshi"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Uchi-mata is part of which Nage no Kata category?",
        "correct_answer": "Ashi-waza",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Te-waza",
            "Koshi-waza",
            "Ma-sutemi-waza"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ura-nage is part of which Nage no Kata category?",
        "correct_answer": "Ma-sutemi-waza",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Koshi-waza",
            "Ashi-waza",
            "Yoko-sutemi-waza"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Yoko-sutemi-waza category in Nage no Kata includes Yoko-gake, Yoko-guruma, and",
        "correct_answer": "Uki-waza",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Uchi-mata",
            "Tomoe-nage",
            "Yoko-tomoe-nage"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many throwing techniques are in each of the Nage no Kata categories?",
        "correct_answer": "3",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "4",
            "5",
            "6"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Koshi-waza category in Nage no Kata includes Tsurikomi-goshi, Harai-goshi, and",
        "correct_answer": "Uki-goshi",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Uki-otoshi",
            "Sumi-gaeshi",
            "Uchi-mata"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Nage no Kata categories are: Te-waza, Koshi-waza, Ashi-waza, Yoko-sutemi-waza, and",
        "correct_answer": "Ma-sutemi-waza",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Shime-waza",
            "Uki-waza",
            "Kansetsu-waza"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Tai-otoshi or body drop belongs to the following Nage no Kata category:",
        "correct_answer": "None",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Ashi-waza",
            "Te-waza",
            "Koshi-waza"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Uki-otoshi Seoi-nage and Kata-guruma belong to which Nage no Kata category?",
        "correct_answer": "Te-waza",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "None",
            "Ashi-waza",
            "Ma-sutemi-waza"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Tomoe-nage, Ura-nage, and Sumi-gaeshi belong to which Nage no Kata category?",
        "correct_answer": "Ma-sutemi-waza",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "None",
            "Te-waza",
            "Koshi-waza"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Yoko-gake, Yoko-guruma, and Uki-waza belong to which Nage no Kata category?",
        "correct_answer": "Yoko-sutemi-waza",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Te-waza",
            "Koshi-waza",
            "Ma-sutemi-waza"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Tai-otoshi, Tsuri-goshi, and O-goshi belong to which Nage no Kata category?",
        "correct_answer": "None",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Te-waza",
            "Koshi-waza",
            "Ashi-waza"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Okuri-ashi-harai, Sasae-trsurikomi-ashi, and Uchi-mata belong to which Nage no Kata category?",
        "correct_answer": "Ashi-waza",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "None",
            "Te-waza",
            "Koshi-waza"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Uki-goshi, Harai-goshi, and Tsurikomi-goshi belong to which Nage no Kata category?",
        "correct_answer": "Koshi-waza",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Te-waza",
            "Ashi-waza",
            "Ma-sutemi-waza"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The Lift pull hip throw (Trusikomi-goshi) is part of which category of Nage no Kata?",
        "correct_answer": "Koshi-waza",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Te-waza",
            "Kansetsu-waza",
            "Ashi-waza"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "This is the total number of throwing techniqes within the Nage no Kata:",
        "correct_answer": "15",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "12",
            "20",
            "18"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "All the throwing techniques have to be demonstrated with right and left side throws.",
        "correct_answer": "Yes",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Only right side",
            " Only left side",
            " No"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many sacrifice techniques groups are there in Nage no Kata?",
        "correct_answer": "Two",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "One",
            "Three",
            "None"
        ]
    }]
}